(Amy:)I'm a cowboy
(Amy:)On a steel horse
l ride
(Amy:)I'm wanted
(Amy:)Wanted
Dead or alive
(Amy:)Sheldon, you're ruining
girIfriend-boyfriend sing-along night.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. I'm looking for a barber
and I'm running out of time.
(Sheldon:)My hair is growing...
(Sheldon:)...at the rate of 4.6 yoctometers
per femtosecond.
(Sheldon:)If you're quiet, you can hear it.
- What about Supercuts?
- No, I tried once.
(Sheldon:)They do men's and women's hair
in the same room at the same time.
(Sheldon:)It's like Sodom and Gomorrah
with mousse.
(Amy:)Well, this isn't a crisis. Why don't
you just let your hair grow out a little?
(Sheldon:)Why don't I let my hair grow out?
(Sheldon:)Why don't I start wearing
Birkenstocks...
...and seeking validation of my opinions
by asking, "Can you dig it?"